forthemommas.com 2012-10-14

# Privacy Policy -

What information do we collect?  
We collect information from you when you respond to a survey or fill out a form.  
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address.  
What do we use your information for?  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:  
; To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature  
How do we protect your information?  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.  
Do we use cookies?  
Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie  
Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.  
To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy here. Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies..  
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.  
Third party links  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.  
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 18 years old or older.  
Your Consent  
By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.  
Changes to our Privacy Policy  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.  
This policy was last modified on 3/9/2011  
www.forthemommas.com

Share This:

This post may contain affiliate links. Read my disclosure policy [here](http://www.forthemommas.com/disclosure-2).
